good morning sir it's my pleasure that
i'm here today in front of you
to introduce myself i'm here and i'm
very much similar to my name
i'm a job level and i don't want anybody
to remain sad in my company
i belongs to patna bihar which is the
oldest city of india and also situated
on the bank of devatanga presently i'm
staying in delhi
which is the capital of india and also
famous for historical classes
coming to my academy i have done my
graduation
from san diego's college in commerce
with 72 percentage
and throughout my education i always
course first division my hobbies
are i like to watch motivational videos
explore new cultures
and also i love to meet with positive
attitude and successful personality
so that i can learn new things from them
i am a pre-med spirit girl my friends
called me for the time
because of my adjustable nature
my aim is to make a career in the
banking sector
as far as as far as my strengths are
concerned
and self-motivated quick learner
hard-working
honest sincere
yes sir i would like to say you
about my family there are five members
in my family
my my grandmother he's the
head of the cat my father is a business
man
my mother is a homemaker i have two
siblings my brother
he's an engineer working with charter
motors
and i have a younger sister
she's working in airline as a family
my strengths are i am self motivated
quickly on this transcendence
my weaknesses are i give more voices
to the first professional life which
happened my personal life
listen so sir
its headquarter is situated in mumbai
and its registration and its registered
office is situated in barodra gujarat
the chairman of icic bank is
christian and the ceo of
icic bank is sunday first
icic bank is
also have lots of branching in india
as well as in foreign
it has 5 528
branches in india and 5
and 15 150
158 areas
this tagline is
because from beginning i have an
interesting background
because the banking sector have a
potential
sector and here we get
lots of opportunity and also
banking sector have good involvement
it also covers our monetary aspects so
that it is necessary for a middle class
girl's
likeness and also get reputation
in a society
listen
[Applause]
commerce is a business where
selling of goods and services are
from sellers to the distributor
there are four types of accounts
deficit accounts deficit
account nri account fix account
deposit account in fixed account
we can save of the save we can save
our fixed amount of money for a
particular period of time